# PABLO MARTIN, LOPEZ

Full Stack Developer



## About me

I want to acquire experience and skills that allow me to grow and continue developing knowledge. Manage to face new challenges by demonstrating my potential, in order to achieve proposed goals in the medium and long term.



+54 1165428432



pablo\_mtv08@hotmail.com



Argentina - Buenos Aires

Age: 29

## **LANGUAGES**

- Español (Nativo)
- Ingles (Intermedio)

## **NETWORKS/WEB**



<u>github.com/pabloApoca</u>



<u>linkedin.com/in/pablo-martin-lopez/</u>



<u>pabloapoca.github.io/mi-portfolio/</u>

## **OPERATING SYSTEMS**

WINDOWS / LINUX

## **LEARNING**

Amazon web services in Udemy

### **EXPERIENCE**

**OverVision Analytics** 

Apr 2022 - Oct 2023

**Full Stack Developer** 

Development of Desktop and Mobile applications. Technologies:

Backend: PHP / Laravel 9.

**Frontend**: VueJs 3 / Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Javascript. **Tools**: Database PostgreSQL / Git-GitLab / Jira/ Scrum.

## **Digital House**

Mar 2021- Jul 2023

## **Backend Programming Technician**

- Mar 2021 Apr 2022 (FULLTIME): Setting up and teaching Backend programming classes in Mercadolibre ang Globant Bootcamps, technologies: Git, Java +11, Golang, Api Rest Spring Boot, Testing, Databases SQL/NoSQL and Scrum methodology.
- <u>Apr 2022 Jul 2023 (PART TIME)</u>: Technical Assistant and content designer in the Digital House career, Certified Tech Developer, along with <u>Mercadolibre</u> and <u>Globant</u> participating in the second year with the **Java** programming language and third year with **Golang**.

### Certant

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

## **Full Stack Developer**

Requirements analysis, software development in **Java** programming language, web development with **Angular** Javascript Framework and development of SQL queries in **MySQL**.

## **EDUCATION**

School of Technical Education N° 3 - Claypole

2009 - 2011

- Bachelor's Degree in Production of Goods and Services.
- Senior Master of Works.

## National University of Lanús - UNLA

2012-2021

Career: Bachelor's degree in systems

- University Programmer Analyst (Completed).
- Bachelor's degree in systems (In progress, I only need the Thesis)

## **COURSES**

- UNLA: Web page design with HTML5 and CSS3..
- Udemy: Development of web systems in PHP 7 OOP, MySQL, Jquery Ajax.
- Quales Group: SQL SERVER Databases.
- **Udemy**: Angular 9/10 for beginners..
- Codo a Codo 4.0 BA: Full Stack PHP development.
- <u>Coursera Universidad AUSTRAL</u>: Server-side development: NodeJS, Express and MongoDB.
- Udemy: CRUD with Laravel, Sweetalert2, Toastr, Vuejs and Axios.
- CUI: English courses, levels 1, 2, 3 and 4 approved.

## **SKILLS**

Java / PHP / Spring Boot / Angular +13 / VueJs 3 HTML 5 / CSS 3 / Boostrap / Tailwind CSS

Api Rest / Databases SQL-noSQL / Scrum / Jira / Git / Postman

## PABLO MARTIN, LOPEZ

## Desarrollador Full Stack



## Sobre mi

Deseo adquirir experiencia y aptitudes que me permitan crecer y seguir desarrollando conocimientos. Lograr enfrentar nuevos desafíos demostrando mi potencial, con el fin de alcanzar metas propuestas a mediano y largo plazo.



+54 1165428432



pablo\_mtv08@hotmail.com



Argentina - Buenos Aires

Edad: 29

## **IDIOMAS**

- Español (Nativo)
- Ingles (Intermedio)

## REDES/WEB



github.com/pabloApoca



<u>linkedin.com/in/pablo-martin-lopez/</u>



pabloapoca.github.io/mi-portfolio/

## SISTEMAS OPERATIVOS

WINDOWS / LINUX

## **APRENDIENDO**

Amazon web services en Udemy

### **EXPERIENCIA**

**OverVision Analytics** 

Abr 2022 - Oct 2023

**Desarrollador Full Stack** 

Desarrollo de aplicaciones de Escritorio y Mobile. Tecnologías:

Backend: PHP / Laravel 9.

Frontend: VueJs 3 / Html / Css / Tailwind CSS / Javascript.

Herramientas: Base de datos PostgreSQL / Git-GitLab / Jira / Scrum.

## **Digital House**

Mar 2021- Jul 2023

## Técnico de Programación Backend

- Mar 2021 Abr 2022 (FULLTIME): Armado y dictado de clases de programación **Backend** en Bootcamps de <u>Mercadolibre</u> y <u>Globant</u>, tecnologías: Git, **Java** +11, **Golang**, Api Rest Spring Boot, Testing, Bases de datos SQL/NoSQL y metodología Scrum.
- <u>Abr 2022 Jul 2023 (PART TIME)</u>: Asistente Técnico y contenidista en la carrera de Digital House, Certified Tech Developer, junto a <u>Mercadolibre y Globant</u> participando en el segundo año con el lenguaje de programación **Java** y tercer año en **Golang**.

### Certant

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

## **Desarrollador Full Stack**

Análisis de requerimientos, desarrollo de Software en lenguaje de programación **Java**, desarrollo web con Framework de **Javascript Angular** y desarrollo de queries sql en **MySQL**.

## **FORMACIÓN**

Escuela de Educación Técnica Nº 3 - Claypole

2009 - 2011

- Bachillerato en Producción de Bienes y Servicios
- Técnico Maestro Mayor de Obras.

## Universidad Nacional de Lanús - UNLA

2012-2021

Carrera: Licenciatura en sistemas

- Analista Programador Universitario (Completado).
- Licenciatura en sistemas (En curso, solo me falta la Tesis).

## **CURSOS**

- UNLA: Diseño de páginas web con HTML5 y CSS3.
- Udemy: Desarrollo de sistemas web en PHP 7 POO, MySQL, Jquery Ajax.
- Quales Group: Bases de Datos SQL SERVER.
- Udemy: Angular 9/10 para principiantes.
- Codo a Codo 4.0 BA: Desarrollo PHP Full Stack.
- <u>Coursera Universidad AUSTRAL</u>: Desarrollo del lado del servidor: NodeJS, Express y MongoDB.
- **Udemy**: CRUD con Laravel, Sweetalert2, Toastr, Vuejs y Axios.
- <u>CUI</u>: Cursos de Inglés, niveles 1, 2, 3 y 4 aprobados.

## **COMPETENCIAS**

Java / PHP / Spring Boot / Angular +13 / VueJs 3 HTML 5 / CSS 3 / Boostrap / Tailwind CSS

Api Rest / Bases de datos SQL-noSQL / Scrum / Jira / Git / Postman